<resources>
    <string name="app_name">exer2_borromeo_b4l</string>
    <string name="header_text">Which cartoon character are you?</string>
    <string name="tv_logo">TV Logo</string>
    <string name="start_text">Start</string>
    <string name="retry_text">Retry</string>
    <string name="agent_p">
        Perry the Platypus, code named Agent P, is Phineas and Ferb\'s pet platypus, who, unbeknownst to his owners, lives a double life as a secret
        agent for the O.W.C.A. (The Organization Without a Cool Acronym a.k.a. "The Agency"), a government organization of animal spies. In the Agency,
        his immediate superior is Major Monogram.
        \n\nPerry appears to be selfless and devoid of vanity. In "The Best Lazy Day Ever", it is only after he turns everything else affected by the
        Ugly-inator back to normal that he reverts himself to his normal state. He deeply cares about the Flynn-Fletcher family and is afraid to lose
        them. He will take immediate action whenever they are threatened ("Journey to the Center of Candace", "Phineas and Ferb Get Busted!", "Oh,
        There You Are, Perry", Phineas and Ferb The Movie: Across the 2nd Dimension, "Where's Perry?", "Where's Perry? (Part Two)", "Phineas and Ferb
        Save Summer"). He is nice to not only his allies but to his nemesis Dr. Doofenshmirtz as well, though only on some occasions
        ("Oil on Candace", "Thaddeus and Thor", "Brain Drain", "Skiddley Whiffers", "When Worlds Collide", "Road to Danville").
    </string>
    <string name="candace">
        Candace Gertrude Flynn is the 15-year-old sister of Phineas Flynn and the step-sister of Ferb Fletcher. The eldest child of the Flynn-Fletcher
        household, she spends large portions of her time striving, but never succeeding to get her brothers in trouble for the things they do every day.
        \n\nA more successful venture that sometimes clashes with or overrides her need to bust her brothers, is her infatuation with Jeremy Johnson.
        While she isn\'t doing these, she would often be seen conversing on the phone, or hanging out with Stacy Hirano and less often Jenny Brown,
        where she usually talks about Jeremy or tries to recruit their help in busting her brothers.
        \n\nCandace has been known to lose her patience very easily and panic at the pettiest of things. For this, Linda attended an author visitation for
        the series, You and Your High Strung Teen by Bridgette Oshinomi. Bridgette herself related with Linda to having a vigorous daughter of her own but
        was officially convinced that Candace was much more unstable than her own daughter after seeing the photo she sent to Linda's cellphone. However,
        she along with Linda remained unaware of the circumstances under which the photo was taken.
    </string>
    <string name="danny_fenton">
        Daniel "Danny" Fenton, also known by his alias Danny Phantom, is the titular protagonist of the television series Danny Phantom. Becoming a
        half-human/half-ghost during a Lab accident, Danny has taken on the role of a ghostly superhero to protect Amity Park and the world from the
        dangerous ghosts of the Ghost Zone.
        \n\nWhen he\'s not worrying about ghosts, Danny is kind, easy-going, helpful, and compassionate at times. He likes using his ghost powers for
        good, but, being a teenage boy, is not always above using them to get revenge on bullies or sneak into the girls' locker room. His ghost
        hunting often cuts into his school work time, but he does work hard when he puts his mind on the task at hand. He loves making puns and
        exchanging witty banter during his fights, and while there's moments when he under-appreciates his friends, he is thankful to have them.
    </string>
    <string name="doofenshmirtz">
        Dr. Heinz Doofenshmirtz, {Dr. D, Dr. Doofenshmirtz, Doofenshmirtz, Heinz or Doof for short, nicknamed Slouchy by Rodney, Heinz the Ocelot,
        Professor Time (around 15 years after the current show time)} is a 47 year old evil scientist hailing from the country of Drusselstein. He is the
        head of Doofenshmirtz Evil Incorporated. He tends not to be evil in the traditional sense, but rather overly dramatic, eccentric and generally
        clueless. His incompetence is showed particularly in "Bullseye!", when he is seen with Rodney discussing Lawrence\'s awful performance, with
        Rodney stating "I didn't think anyone could be more incompetent at being evil than you", and Heinz replying, "Me neither". His usual lair is an
        office building that he apparently owns, though he\'s worked from other locations when necessary for his plans. He attempts to wreak generally
        "evil" havoc and assert his rule across the entire Tri-State Area. Despite true dedication to this mission, almost all of his plans have been
        thwarted by his nemesis Perry the Platypus, though a few turn out to be successful in nature. (Doofenshmirtz has become so used to this foiling
        that he tends to feel empty or upset on the few occasions where Perry does not stand in his way). Dr. Doofenshmirtz seems to quite enjoy musical
        numbers, and has performed songs about "impressing his professor" and how he hates his brother among other subjects. Though most of his plans are
        frequently flawful at best and his doctorate was purchased off the internet, some of his inventions (almost always suffixed with "-inator") have
        been fairly impressive and successful. Online, Doofenshmirtz goes by the names of StrudelCutie4427, and JohnnyRingoenshmirtz217.
    </string>
    <string name="grim">
        The Grim Reaper (or just Grim) is the protagonist of the franchise. He is an undead skeleton personification of Death, who speaks with a
        Jamaican accent. After having lost to Billy and Mandy after Mandy cheated in a limbo contest over the soul of Mr. Snuggles (and also the soul
        of Billy himself), Grim is now forced to be their best friend forever. If Grim does not live up to his commitment, he will be stripped of his
        powers and be forced to spend eternity in Underworld Jail.
        \n\nGrim is often stuck with cleaning-up the consequences of mishaps that are in no small part due to Billy's stupidity and lack of common
        sense. On Mandy's part, Grim is often forced to do her chores and obey her direct orders, as her unwilling slave. It is stated several times in
        the series that he does the dishes every single day for Billy and Mandy ever since they first met which he seriously despises.
    </string>
    <string name="kuzco">
        Kuzco (also known as Emperor Kuzco) is the protagonist of Disney\'s 2000 animated feature film, The Emperor\'s New Groove. He is the Emperor of
        the Inca Empire in Peru, known for his arrogant and saucy personality. When his ruthless behavior gets him transformed into a talking llama, Kuzco
        slowly comes to realize the error of his ways.
        \n\nKuzco is initially portrayed as an arrogant, comically conceited, selfish, cocky, sarcastic teenager, albeit with a sense of flair, style, and
        pizzazz, as he never takes his job as emperor too seriously. His nature was petty such as having an old man thrown out of the window (but not
        killing him) simply because Kuzco blamed him for "ruining his groove" in the opening song (when Kuzco bumped into him due to not being aware of his
        surroundings), as well as sadistically taunting Pacha with the destruction of the latter's village before having him escorted out when revealing
        his plans to create Kuzcotopia. He also was initially unwilling to marry any girls who didn't meet his image, often bluntly and rudely dismissing
        them, as evidenced by the opening of the movie where he had to choose the bride, and refused them just from brief glances. It is implied that this
        personality stemmed from the fact that Yzma practically raised him from childhood. However, it is also shown that his selfish ways were a cover-up
        for his yearning for a family, which he never had.
    </string>
    <string name="mr_krabs">
        Eugene Harold Krabs, simply and more commonly known as Mr. Krabs, is one of the ten main characters in the SpongeBob SquarePants franchise.
        He is a red crab who lives in an anchor with his daughter, Pearl, who is a whale. He is the owner and founder of the Krusty Krab restaurant as
        well as the employer of both SpongeBob and Squidward.
        \n\nMr. Krabs is extremely greedy and obsessed with money to the point where he occasionally treats money better than his employees and
        daughter. The series exaggerates Mr. Krabs\' greed, with him often anthropomorphizing money. Mr. Krabs is mostly respected by SpongeBob, who
        sees him as a father figure, while Squidward tends to loathe him.
        \n\nMr. Krabs' nemesis and business rival is Sheldon J. Plankton, co-owner of the Chum Bucket with his wife Karen. Plankton was Krabs' best
        friend during childhood, but he is now bent on stealing the Krabby Patty secret formula that makes the Krusty Krab so successful.
    </string>
    <string name="patrick_star">
        Patrick Star is one of the ten main characters of the SpongeBob SquarePants series. He is SpongeBob\'s best friend as well as one of his two
        neighbors.
        \n\nHe lives under a rock in the underwater city of Bikini Bottom. SpongeBob and Squidward are his two neighbors, with one on each side of
        his residence.
        \n\nBoth he and SpongeBob like to bother Squidward; though they do it unknowingly and have good intentions. He is the son of Herb and
        Margie Star and the brother of Sam Star.
    </string>
    <string name="sam_manson">
        Samantha "Sam" Manson is one of Danny\'s best friends. She is a self-proclaimed Goth who is fascinated with the subliminal and netherworldly,
        and is a very outspoken ultra-recyclo-vegetarian.
        \n\nSam\'s personality is less dreary than the stereotypical "goth" persona that is usually shown. She can be rational, sarcastic, forceful,
        bossy, passionate, strong-willed, but also good-hearted and caring. Based on how she conducts herself, it would be fairer to say that she
        labels herself a goth more as an outlet for her independence and individuality than as an embrace of how the stereotypical goth is presumed to
        behave. She isn't spoiled and would rather earn real friends instead of dealing with the popularity and fake friendships that come with
        wealth.
    </string>
    <string name="taylor_hebert">
        Taylor Anne Hebert is the main character of Worm.
        \n\nShe is an exceptionally accomplished martial artist; her bug-swarm-enhanced senses enable her to react to events faster than a normal
        human should be able to. She can easily defeat even other experienced parahumans in hand-to-hand combat. The boost to her senses and
        coordination due to her swarm also allows her exceptional accuracy with firearms. Personality-wise, she is noted to be cold, distant,
        exceptionally driven, and even ruthless by many characters.
        \n\nShe became concerned that her passenger was influencing her behaviour. She even blamed ordinary emotions on her passenger. She tried
        hypnosis and bartering with it to control it, to no avail. Eventually she made a kind of peace with it.
    </string>
</resources>
